Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Val. as of 10/01/1962 and Subsequent Censuses, 1953 June 23-1962 October 01 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L489.16B
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val.-Trust Fund, 1964 October 01-1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L489.17
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Census Data,Cost Calclations,and Projections, 1964 October 01 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L489.17A
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -General, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L491.1
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: - Census and Pension Calculations, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L491.2
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -,Projections, 1950-1960 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L491.3
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Valuation as of 10/01/1954, 1954 October 01 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L491.4
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Personnel Records,(received 1955), undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L491.5
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Val. as of 06/01/1955, 1955 June 01 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L491.6
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Non-vesting Services Table,Val. as of 06/01/1955, 1955 June 01 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L491.6a
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Vesting service table,Val as of 06/01/1955, 1955 June 01 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L491.6b
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Retirement Trust Agreement, Amendments, 1956 October (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L491.7
  - Papers, undated (Box 37)
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Valuation as of 1959, 1959 June 30 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L491.8
  - KAISER METAL PRODUCTS: -Fleetwings Guards ' Pension Plan; Pension Agreement w/ U.A.W.-A.F.L.-C.I.O., 1959-1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L491.9
  - From the Office of Bredhoff,Cushman,Gottesman,and Cohen,Articles, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L493
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L494.1
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L494.1a
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan Calculations, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L494.1b
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan, Amendments, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L494.1c
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Death Benefit Fund, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L494.2
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan Valuation as of 07/31/1955, 1955 July 31 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L494.3
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: -Pension Plan Valuation as of Census of Employees, 1955 July 31 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L494.3a
  - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BRIDGE STRUCTURAL AND ORNAMENTAL IRON WORKERS: - Amendment to Staff Retirement Plan, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L494.4
  - BRIDGE AND IRON WORKERS: - Pension Plan Valuation, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L494.5
  - Brookings Institute, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L495
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Staff Pension Plan, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L495.1
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Staff Pension Plan Calculations, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L495.1a
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -36th Annual Convention,-Report, 1948 May 17 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L495.1b
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Interwoven Stocking Company, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L495.2
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Interwoven Stocking Company, I.B.M. Tabulations, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L495.2a
  - Papers, undated (Box 38)
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Hosiery Industry Employees Pension Plan, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L495.3
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: - Hosiery Ind. Employees Pension Plan, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L495.3a
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: - Hosiery Ind. Employees Pension Plan Wage Tribunal Documents, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L495.3b
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Pension Calculations, Female, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L495.3c
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Hosiery Empl. Pension Plan,Exposure and Withdrawals Based on Social Security Samples, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L495,3d
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -Hos. Empl. Pension Plan, Valuation, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L495.3e
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF HOSIERY WORKERS: -1959 Amendments and Valuation,160 Amendments, 1959 January 01 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L495.3f
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Rairoad Retirement Legislation, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L496.1
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Statements Submitted to House and Senate Committees, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L496.1a
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L496.1b
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation-Calculations, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L496.1bl
  - Papers, undated (Box 39)
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation, 1953 January-July (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L496.1c
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation, 1953 August-December (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L496.1cl
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation- Calculations, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L496.1d
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L496.1e
  - FOUR COOPERATIVE RAILROAD BROTHERHOODS: -Proposed Railroad Retirement Legislation, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L496.lf
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Railway and Steamship Clerks,Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees; Staff Retirement Plan, 1955 June (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L498
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Supplementary Pension:Plan, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L498.1
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Supplementary Pension:Plan-,Census and Cards for 1955 Cost Calculations, 1954 June 30 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L498.la
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Supplementary Pension: Plan- Cost Calculations, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L498.lb
  - Papers, undated (Box 40)
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Supplementary Pension:PlanValuation,,Based on 1% Last Five Years Average, 1955 July (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L498.1c
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Submission to Internal Revenue Service, 1955 December (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L498.1d
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: - Staff Retirement Plan -Valuation as of 12/31/1958, 1958 December 31 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L498.2
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: - Staff Retirement Plan -Valuation as of Census of Employees, 1958 December 31 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L498.2a
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: - Staff Retirement Plan Val.,,Summary, Per Capitas, Numerators, 1953 December 31 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L498.2b
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: - Valuation, 1962 December 31 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L498.3
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Valuation, Card Census, 1962 December 31 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L498.3a
  - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS: -Final Average of Salary Amendment, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L498.4
  - San Francisco Printing Industry, Welfare Fund, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L501
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Relations, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L502
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, (I.U.E.), undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L502.18a
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: Local Officials Pension Plan, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L503.1
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: -Local Officials Pension Plan-Preliminary Report-Prepared by M.W.L., 1957 April 09 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L503.1a
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: -Clerical Employees and'Officers, Valuation, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L503.2
  - Papers, undated (Box 41)
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: -Headquarters'Plan, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L503.3
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: -Headquarters ' Plan, Calculations Based on Census, 1957 July 01 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L503.3a
  - INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF TEAMSTERS: -Pension Plans and Summaries, Local Unions and Joint Councils, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L503.4
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Analysis of Health Insurance Plan, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L504.1
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Summary Information-Insurance Co. and Blue Cross/Blue Shield Bids, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L504.2a
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Summary Information-Insurance Co. and Blue Cross/Blue Shield Bids, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L504.2b
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Aetna Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L504.3
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Blue Cross/ Blue Shield, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L504.4
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Continental Casualty Co., undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L504.5
  - Papers, undated (Box 42)
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Equitable Life Assurance Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L504.6
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Liberty Mutual Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L504.7
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Metropolitan Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L504.8
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Mutual of Omaha, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L504.9
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -New York Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L504.9a
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Prudential Ins. Co. of America, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L504.11
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Travelers Ins. Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L504.12
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Union Labor Life Ins Co., undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L504.13
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Health Insurance andBlue Cross/Blue Shield -Material, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L504.14
  - NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES: -Buffalo Blue Cross, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L504.15
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Retired Life, Hospital and Surgical Insurance-Correspondence, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L505.1
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: Calculations, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L505.la
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Taxibility of Insurance Companies, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L505.2
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Pension Plans, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L505.3
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Pension Plans ,Calculations, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L505.3A
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Insurance Plan, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L505.4
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Joint Insurance Fund, Glass'Bottle Blowers Association, Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L505.5
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Miscl. and Labor Department Reports, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L505.6
  - Papers, undated (Box 43)
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Work Sheets and Calculations, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L505.7
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Censuses and IBM tabulations, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L505.8
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Staff Pension Plan, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L505.9
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Benefits for Retired Employees-Martin E. Segal & Co., undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L505.9a
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Report by M.W. Latimer, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L505.11
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Report by M.W. Latimer, Pension Plan, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L505.12
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -MORTALITY AT 4 1/2%, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L505.13
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS: -Service Tables at 4 1/2 %, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L505.14
  - GLASS-CONTAINER MANUFACTURERS, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L505.15
  - Maryland Department of Licensing and Regulation Insurance Division, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L506. 1A
  - UNITED BROTHERHOOD OF CARPENTERS AND JOINERS: -Retirement and Pension Plan, Valuation as of 06/01/1962, 1962 June 01 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L507
  - UNITED BROTHERHOOD OF CARPENTERS AND JOINERS: -Retirement and Pension Plan,Valuation as of 06/01/1962 Calculations, 1962 June 01 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L507.1
  - CARPENTERS WELFARE FUND: -Analysis of Fund, 1958 March 31 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L508
  - CARPENTERS WELFARE FUND: -Increase in Insurance Benefits, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L508.1
  - MONTGOMERY COUNTY BOARD OF EDUCATION: -Litigation, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L509
  - MONTGOMERY COUNTY BOARD OF EDUCATION: -Litigation, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L509.12
  - Papers, undated (Box 44)
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): -Pension Valuation, 1958-1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L510.1
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): -Pension Valuation, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L510.1A
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): -Joe Musher,Miscl.,Material on Pension Valuation, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L510.2
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation, MWL Service Table and Commutation Functions-Basic Rates, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L510.3
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation-Census Multiplications Summary Valuations, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L510.4
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation-Take Home Calculations, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L510.5
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation-N.Y. State Service Table; Reconciliation; State Factors; Investment Data; History, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L510.6
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation-Per Capitas, MW.L. Service Table, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L510.7
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): - Valuation-Comparative Pensions,Private and State Systems, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L510.8
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES ASSOCIATION INC(CSEA): Miscl. Calculations to CSEA Major Report,Draft Material Included, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L510. 8A
  - Papers, undated (Box 45)
  - Insurance Plan Valuation, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L511
  - Insurance Contracts and Amendments, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L511.1
  - Group Life Insurance Program, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L511.2
  - Group Life Insurance Program Specifications and Responses, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L511.2A
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Correspondence, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L512.1
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Occidental Financial and Experience Reports, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L512.1a
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Occidental Contracts, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L512.1b
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Basic Data, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L512.1c
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Calculations for 1959 Report (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L512.1d
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan-Photo Stat of Census Cards for 1959 Report (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L512.1e
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Representative Retirement Plan- Report, 1959 June 30 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L512.lf
  - Papers, undated (Box 46)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Coates, Herfurth, & England Actuarial Tables and other Actuarial Data, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L512.2
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Collectively Bargained Health, Welfare, and Pension Plans, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L512.3
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Correspondence, (life with Dues and Group Insurance), undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L512.4
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Health and Welfare Report, 1959 June 12 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L512.4a
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Life with Dues Report, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L512.4b
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Life with Dues Pre 1959, Age Distributions (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L512.4c
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Life with Dues-Recent Age Distribution Data, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L512.4d
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Life with Dues-Calculations for 1959 Report (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L512.4e
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Life With Dues Miscl Data, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L512.4f
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Preparation of Life with Dues Speculation, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L512.5
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Analysis of Insurance Programs-Specifications, (Group Insurance; Executive Health and Welfare), 1959 October (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L512.5a
  - Papers, undated (Box 47)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Aetna Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Equitable Life Assurance Society, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b1
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Golden State Mutual Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b2
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Hospital Service Of California, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b3
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -John Hancock Mutual Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b4
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Metropolitan Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b5
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -North American Life and Casulty Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L512,5b6
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Occidental Life Ins. Co. of California, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L512,5b7
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Prudential Ins. Co. of America, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b8
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -United Benefit Life Insurance Co. (Mutual of Omaha), undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L512.5b9
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Southland Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Union Labor Life Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Travelers Ins. Co., undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Report on Analysis of Bids Recieved From Insurance Companies, 1959 December 07 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L512.5c
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Executive Health and Welfare Rlan.Effective 01/01/1960Correspondence, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L512.6
  - Papers, undated (Box 48)
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Retired Employees' Health and Welfare Program, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L512.7
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Pension Benefits for Direct Hire Employees(clerical), undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L512.8
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Pension Plan for Local Union 856, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L512.9
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Health and Welfare for Retired Members of Local 595, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L512.9a